Today I want to see the most
impressive square you have made yourself.
And I think we should start with Karin.
This is a screenshot of my Strava.
-And it's a running app.
-Yes, that's right.
So you can see which
formation you can end up running in.
-And what formation is that?
-It's a square.
That was great.
I have been running this route five days a week-
-for the past two months to perfect..
--for the past two months to perfect...
-Is that true?
-Yes. Angles and speed.
I have run outside in sleet,
snow, on ice, in wind and weather.
I fell in Kirkeveien in front of the 20-bus.
I will apologize to the lady
in Bogstadveien with a stroller.
I ran into you and screamed: "Track."
You got really scared, you had a child.